[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Hey, what's your name again?
It's Mungkorn.
- Mungkorn?
- Yes, sir.
What are you singing?
I'll go with 'Wai Jai Dai Gah.'
Wai Jai Dai Gah?
- Yeah.
- Alright, then.
♪Back in the day,
wherever we went wandering,♪
♪We were always together,
laughing at everything♪
♪But then you met that city girl,♪
♪That's when you'd do anything
just to please her♪
♪Can those red lips really be trusted?♪
♪Can that pretty face
really be trusted?♪
♪Coming from so far away,
can she be trusted?♪
♪She's not me,
can she really be trusted?♪
You were great, Mungkorn.
Thanks.
And what about that guy?
You're not returning
to your table, are you?
Can we have a toast before I go?
- Sure.
- My boy wants me. I've gotta go.
Okay.
See you around.
I had no idea
you had such a great voice, Mungkorn.
Hey.
You called me back here...
cause you wanted me
to flirt with you instead, right?
I just wanted to remind you
what we're actually here for today.
Thear, if you keep buying drinks
for every girl here,
you're gonna get wasted for real.
I'm not that drunk. I'm good.
I knew it.
I'm fine. I'm good.
Anyway, where's the bathroom?
Better safe than sorry.
I'll take you.
Hey, you're acting like I'm wasted.
I'm fine.
If you're not,
then what's gotten into you?
- You guys wait here.
- I'm good.
Whoa, hold on a sec.
Are you okay?
- Ins...
- S... Sweetheart?
Wow, you're really calling me that?
I'm kinda getting a good buzz.
Should we go for it?
Right here?
If you say so.
I'm getting pretty tipsy, too.
Hey...
I'm getting the chills.
I'm feeling it now.
How do you feel?
You've got a nice ass.
Are they all gone yet?
- Not yet.
- Keep going.
Are they gone now?
They're all gone.
Look,
we don't know
who's working with them.
Whatever you're going to call me,
you'd better be careful.
Yes, Inspector.
My bad.
Has the informant sent the intel yet?
Yes. His name is Ronnaphop.
He's suspected to be
the leader of the Black Bull gang,
the major drug dealer in this area.
Informant says he should be
getting to this club around midnight.
He's the real deal, huh?
I'd say he's almost
as good-looking as me.
This is the photo from his social media.
This is him.
Damn, he edited it so much
he looks like a different person.
(The Black Bull has entered the cave.)
Let's go.
- Wait, Inspector.
- Hey, stop calling me that.
Your fly is open.
Just when I'm in a rush. Seriously?
We're running out of time.
It's just... stuck.
It won't budge.
Please allow me to help you.
Help how?
Stay still.
I'll give the signal.
Three, two, one.
All set.
Yeah, thanks a lot.
Let's move.
Go.
Shall we start the operation now?
No.
This is my specialty.
Leave it to me.
Oh...
Hi, boss.
Mind if I join you for a dance?
Not at all.
Fair skin's always been my weakness.
Aw, you're such a smooth talker.
Wow, your hands are so soft.
Easy there, boss.
Wait, you're a cop?
Freeze!
Stop!
Get on your knees!
You're under arrest for drug trafficking
and organized crime.
- Get down!
- You have the right to remain silent.
- Stay down!
- Anything you say
can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
Oh, but if you do talk,
you're getting busted anyway, boss.
- You've got no proof.
- Keep your mouth shut.
Sarge!
How was that?
(Inspector Thear:
The cunning and irresistible inspector)
All suspects are in custody
along with the evidence.
Hey, hey!
- Stay still!
- What is wrong with you?
Hey!
- Inspector!
- Sarge, get out of there.
He might be faking it.
I don't think he is.
His lips are turning blue.
Listen to me. Get away from him.
We should save him first,
or it'll be too late.
- Hey!
- Excuse me, Inspector.
Inspector!
Please call an ambulance.
I am.
Hey, stay still.
- Freeze!
- Drop the gun.
- Drop it.
- I told you to drop the damn gun!
Drop it!
Okay, okay.
Put it on...
Ugh!
(Sergeant Mungkorn:
Kind but not easy to break)
(Inspector Phuwin: Fierce, tough,
and intense. The pride of Mae Sai.)
(Sergeant Lukplub: The youngest
but not the weakest, Phuwin's babe)
Inspector, he's getting away!
Hey!
Goddammit!
Sh*t!
F*ck...
Go. Get up there.
Come on.
Go up there.
- I'll leave this to you, Lieutenant.
- Yes, sir.
Good luck, boss.
Thanks a lot, Mungkorn.
If you hadn't backed me up,
I would've been in deep trouble.
I should be apologizing to you
for disobeying your orders.
The whole plan almost fell apart.
You get it now?
Don't be so stubborn next time.
You need to listen to me.
It was pretty fun, though.
We don't get to work together often.
It reminds me of the old days.
Did Phuwin and Lukplub already leave?
Oh, they already did.
They left together.
Man, what is it with couples?
Don't they get sick of each other?
Aren't they too clingy?
As if you don't want a partner yourself.
Well, I really don't.
Come on, I value my freedom.
Having to worry about someone?
No, thanks.
I'd rather stay single.
It's way easier.
All those words, and what you mean
is that you're a flirt, huh?
Wait, maybe you just
haven't found the one.
And what about you?
Have you found them?
Have you found the one?
Watch out! A gun!
Inspector!
Inspector, hang in there.
Help!
Inspector!
Inspector Thear!
(Yin as Theartha)
(War as Mungkorn)
(Shane as Phuwin)
(Boss as Lukplub)
(Kit as Kanin)
(Tang as Nadol)
(Tae as Saming)
Your blood pressure is normal.
My blood pressure might be fine,
but my heart rate certainly isn't.
So, do you have a boyfriend?
Oh, Sarge.
Man, you're such a buzzkill.
I was just about to get an answer
on whether the nurse was single or not.
Your visitor is here,
so I'll take my leave now.
That's two smiles in the bag.
She might be taken.
Your shoulder's been shot,
yet you still have the energy
to flirt with the nurse?
I don't flirt with my shoulder.
I use my mouth.
And I'm kind of famous
for what I can do with it.
Anyway, thanks for looking after me
even though you didn't have to.
I'm just doing my duty
as your subordinate.
Doing your duty, huh?
But I'm not even your direct superior.
I'll just take it as...
you're doing it because you care.
Where is he? Is he awake?
Thear, my boy.
Thear!
- My baby!
- Whoa, Mom. My shoulder!
- My left shoulder.
- How are you? Are you okay?
Hi, Mr. Thear...
Where does it hurt?
- My left shoulder, Mom.
- Where? Here?
Yeah, around here. Don't touch it.
But I'm fine.
It's nowhere near my heart.
It's a piece of cake.
Good afternoon, Lady Pharada.
I'm Sergeant Mungkorn,
Inspector Thear's subordinate.
I'm also...
the reason he got shot.
I am really sorry.
Hey, Sarge. Don't be so dramatic.
That thug was just shooting blindly.
But I think you're seriously
out of luck this time.
Or maybe...
fate is really coming for you
just like the oracle said?
What fate are you talking about, Mom?
It's not that serious.
Not that serious?
This is basically "Final Destination."
Cupid.
On it.
Damn, my car just broke down
out of nowhere.
Whoa!
Hey! You just hit a cop!
You're delivering me food?
It's you. You killed my dad!
I didn't.
I almost died.
- There are more scenarios, too.
- Enough.
I'm a police officer, Mom.
Taking risks is just part of the job.
But if that thug's aim
had been off by just a tiny bit...
Stop it.
And...
if the bullet had hit your heart,
you'd literally be gone.
I don't care.
I'm certain this incident
is a sign of your luck.
As soon as you're discharged,
we're going to see the family oracle.
- Cupid, book an appointment.
- Will do.
That's nonsense, Mom.
I'm not going.
You know I don't believe in oracles.
Every time we go,
she just talks a load of rubbish.
She's just scamming us for money.
- So, no booking yet?
- No! You have to go.
No matter what,
your life is on the line here.
It doesn't make sense.
It's a waste of time.
I'm doing this for your own sake.
If it's for my sake,
you need to stop being so superstitious.
Thear!
You just don't understand
a mother's heart.
Let's go, Cupid.
Man, they're being
way too dramatic about this.
It's not that big of a deal.
If you didn't have anyone
caring about you,
you'd really feel the difference.
What's that supposed to mean?
You're lucky, Inspector,
to have a mother who cares so much
and tries to fix things for you.
She's genuinely terrified of losing you.
I think...
even if you don't believe in oracles,
taking just one day
to give her some peace of mind
shouldn't be too much
of a hassle, right?
So, you're taking her side?
Fine. I'll go.
But you're coming with me.
Wait, what do I have to do with this?
Well, didn't you say you felt guilty?
This is your chance to make it up to me.
(Mother Tongnuan's Shrine)
Gosh, this bad luck
won't give you a break, will it?
I literally just
got out of the hospital.
We could've at least waited
until the wound healed.
Come on.
Mother Tongnuan will keep you
safe and sound.
She's incredibly accurate.
Last time, she predicted
that I'd get a boyfriend.
The very next day, I lost my virginity!
That's just because
you were being such a flirt!
Let's just get this over with
so we can go back to our lives
and so you can stop
being so superstitious.
Disrespectful the moment you arrive?
Even if you don't believe,
you should show some respect, Inspector.
Goodness, thank you
for scolding him for me.
You're amazing.
How did you manage to bring my son here?
Even though I'm his mother,
he wouldn't listen to me.
We're here.
I'll wait right here, then.
You've finally arrived.
This is my son.
He's been having
a run of bad luck lately.
I already know without you telling me.
I can smell the stench of misfortune
from miles away.
What do you see, Mother?
What's going to happen to Mr. Thear?
Your fate has been cursed since birth.
Saturn is looming over your fate,
and so is Uranus.
What does that mean, Mother?
It means...
fate will take everything you own...
even your life.
And...
is there any way to remedy this, Mother?
You must find your soulmate
from your past life.
Then you must marry that person
with heaven and earth as witnesses.
Otherwise...
it won't just be choking on a meatball
or getting shot in the shoulder.
But it will lead to your death
within six months.
- Six months?
I'm passing out.
My Lady!
Young man, would you like
to make merit for your birthday?
Of course.
You must marry someone born on Monday,
the 13th of October.
Both their first and last names
must contain 'ro ruea'.
Otherwise,
this misfortune will follow you
until the day you die.
So you mean he has to get married?
Yes.
You must hold a wedding ceremony
and live together for six months.
Then, your bad luck and karma
will finally be over.
And you expect me
to just marry some stranger?
Mom, are you crazy?
How is that supposed to help?
If he doesn't believe it,
then let him be.
He'll eventually come back to me.
With a description that specific,
where am I supposed to find them?
Oh, should I ask the district chief?
Have him pull up everyone's
birth records in the country?
Fine.
Well, if you're really that good,
why don't you just hand them to me
on a silver platter?
Bring that person to me,
so I don't have to
waste my time looking.
Serve them right up.
(Mr. Mungkorn Phianwanich,
born on Monday, October 13, 1997)
Born on Monday, October 13th.
Mr. Mungkorn...
That consonant is in it.
Phianwanich...
There's another one in that, too!
This is...
That's mine.
The wind is so strong.
It blew this quite a long way.
Wait, Mungkorn.
Is something the matter?
Thear, I've found your soulmate!
A gift from heaven,
no district chief needed.
You need to marry Mungkorn.
- What?
Mom, stop thinking about
that ridiculous marriage right now.
It's only for six months.
You can just get a divorce
once the six months are up.
Only six months?
I'm not going to waste my time
on some superstition of yours.
If word gets out that I'm married,
all the girls I've been seeing
will disappear.
I've been on fire lately.
Yeah, but it's hellfire
that's been following you around.
There's no way, Mom.
How can I marry someone I don't love?
Just get married first,
and you can work on
the relationship later.
That sounds so old-fashioned.
What century do you think we're in?
It doesn't matter.
Fate and fortune
have existed in every age.
You don't have a choice.
- I do!
- No, you don't.
- No.
- I do!
- You don't!
- What about me?
- You...
Do I still have a choice?
Even though I'm just a junior officer
who's supposed to follow orders
and protect my superior,
it's still my life, too.
I only want to
marry someone I truly love.
Someone who'll stay by my side,
listen to me,
share the good and bad with me,
and spend our lives together.
I don't want to marry Inspector Thear.
Mungkorn...
Honey, look...
I really don't want to
force anyone into anything,
but you understand a mother's concern,
don't you?
Yes.
Could you please reconsider?
Is there anything you want?
Just name it, and it's yours.
The necklace from Titanic?
I'll go dive for it myself.
That won't be necessary.
It's just...
I understand your feelings,
Lady Pharada.
But marriage is a huge commitment.
I think you should find someone else
to marry him.
There must be plenty of other people
born at the exact same time
as me.
No, there aren't.
- I'm sure there are.
- No.
I'm really sorry.
I have to head off to work
in Mae Sai now.
Please excuse me, Lady Pharada.
I'll be going now, Inspector.
Can I leave now?
To where?
Oh...
You can leave, Mr. Thear.
But you'd better be careful
because danger lurks
in every step you take.
My Lady, what are we going to do now?
You've underestimated me, Thear.
There's no way I'm going to
let anything happen to my son.
Just you wait and see.
(Police Accommodation, Chiang Rai)
Not tasty, Mungkorn?
I ordered your favorite Northern laab
to welcome you back.
It's tasty.
It's just my stomach's
been a bit upset lately.
Can't enjoy spicy food now.
Phu's just like you.
He has a sensitive stomach,
yet he won't stop.
I always have to keep antacids
ready for him.
He's so stubborn.
And whose babe are you?
I wonder who takes such good care of me.
You guys are so cheesy.
Hey, let me ask you something.
Have you ever thought
about getting married?
Of course we have.
But we're in no rush, right?
We're already happy
with the life we have together.
What about you, Phu?
I want to marry you, too.
Why wouldn't I want to
marry my baby?
Hypothetically, if you had to
marry someone you didn't love,
would you still do it?
Why are you asking that?
Oh, no reason.
I was just thinking about
when they had arranged marriages.
I wonder how people back then
managed to get through it.
I guess there were
many things involved.
In the past, living as a couple
was probably more practical
than being single.
And then there's the financial side.
If you find a good partner,
they can probably lead you
toward a better life, right?
It's actually a lot like a blind box.
We were just lucky enough
to pull each other.
We're both secret characters, aren't we?
Yeah.
- This one's good. Have you tried it?
- Oh, yeah?
Here, try this one.
Is it good?
Want some sticky rice?
Hi, Mom. What are you up to?
(I'm just folding laundry.)
Hey, let me send you something.
Hold on a sec.
(Hmm? What are you sending me?)
Just a second.
Whoa.
How does Dad look so young?
It's an edited photo.
He passed away so young.
That's why he looks so young
in the photo.
Is technology really
this advanced these days?
Whoa, you picked out quite a big house.
It would be great
if we could live in Phayao together.
Mungkorn, you're just a subordinate.
You have to stay
wherever they tell you to.
(Just do what you can, okay?)
Can't I at least dream?
But dreams need a little luck
to go with them, sweetie.
Mom, what's wrong?
I'm fine, sweetie.
I'm just coughing.
(The weather's starting to get chilly.)
(I'll head to bed in a bit.)
(Talk to you later, okay?)
(I miss you, sweetie.)
Make sure to take your medicine.
Talk to you later.
Okay. God bless you.
(Mr. Mungkorn Phianwanich,
born on Monday, October 13, 1997)
(Is there anything you want?
Just name it, and it's yours.)
(The necklace from Titanic?
I'll go dive for it myself.)
Whoa!
Cupid, what are you doing here?
I'm not Cupid. Call me Somrak.
And who the hell is this?
And this is Bee.
- We're both ready to look after you
- twenty-four hours a day.
Ugh, no way!
You don't have a choice.
For your safety, you need bodyguards.
I insist.
Why?
You're supposed to do it on this side.
Sh*t...
Hey, stop right there!
- Inspector, quick!
- I'm coming!
- Stop, Mr. Thear.
- Wait!
- It's dangerous!
- Mr. Thear, don't go.
- Mr. Thear, it's dangerous!
- Inspector...
- Follow me!
- Hold on. Don't go.
- If Lady Pharada finds out, I'm dead.
- Please don't go.
- Don't go. It's dangerous.
- It's too dangerous!
What the hell is this?
Inspector Thear,
are those two being newly assigned here?
I've seen them
hanging around the station all day.
My mother sent them, sir.
She's been very stressed
and paranoid lately,
so she insisted on
having people protect me.
Whatever you do,
make sure it's appropriate.
We're police officers.
We're supposed to serve the people,
not have the people taking care of us.
It's ruining our professional image.
Yes, sir.
I'll deal with this immediately.
Good.
(Police Major Theartha Phiromsamorn,
Investigative Inspector)
I'm done with this.
How am I supposed to work
if someone's
following me around all day?
But nothing bad happened today, right?
See? This works best.
I'm a police officer.
I can't have someone
watching over me day and night.
What are the locals
going to think of me?
Why don't you understand me at all?
Then what do you want me to do?
You won't get married.
You won't let anyone protect you.
If I could die in your place,
I would have done it already.
Mom...
Can you please try to understand me?
I want to attend your wedding,
not your funeral.
Oh, dear.
My Lady...
You have only one son,
and he's both stubborn and mischievous.
He never sees his mother's great love.
♪Think of all the love a mother gave,♪
- ♪What could ever be enough♪
- ♪To match what she gave?♪
- ♪Oh...♪
- It's only for six months, son.
Just six short months.
Could you please reconsider
just one more time?
(Chiang Rai)
Oh, Lieutenant Prang,
please take these documents
downstairs for me.
What should we have for dinner?
How about some noodles?
No, I'm bored of that.
What do you want, then?
It's up to you.
Up to me?
Then, can I eat you instead?
I want you all day long. Can I eat you?
- I don't know.
- You don't?
Come here.
You're so adorable.
Hey! This is a government building.
What do you think you're doing?
I'll arrest you both.
Good afternoon.
How can I find a love like this, buddy?
You want the truth?
Someone like you
isn't likely to ever settle down.
Still a smart-ass as always.
Anyway, what brings you
all the way to Mae Sai?
Wait, did you miss me?
Not you,
but Sergeant Mungkorn.
Please marry me.
Inspector Thear?
I've been thinking it over.
If I have to have bodyguards
tailing me for six months,
I'd rather just get married
and be done with it.
It won't be a bother to anyone else.
It will be a bother to me.
Why?
Is it because you're dating someone?
Well, no.
You're my boss,
and I'm just your subordinate.
Hey, how is that a problem?
It's perfectly fine.
I might not be as popular as you are,
but I still cherish my freedom.
Marrying me is a bigger deal
than getting a promotion.
Anyone would jump at the chance
to take my last name.
Well, count me out.
Excuse me.
Hey, wait!
Please help me. I'm begging you.
I'll give you anything you want.
What do you want?
Do you want me to get down on one knee
and propose?
Fine, I'll do it right now.
What are you doing, Inspector?
Hey!
Sergeant Mungkorn,
will you marry me?
I, Inspector Thear, solemnly swear...
that I will be
a good husband to you forever.
No way, Inspector.
Come on, I'm begging you.
Please help this handsome
but cursed Inspector.
Please?
What is it with you?
This is a huge deal for me.
If anyone finds out, my life is ruined.
Don't worry. No one will ever find out,
except for our families.
Please help me out.
Inspector, stand up.
Please, just get up.
If you want me to marry you,
I have three conditions.
Name them.
First,
you have to give me one million baht.
Whoa, one million?
Wow, you're really
making the most of this.
I'm gonna use it
to have a house built for my mom.
A good son. I like that.
Second,
once we move to Chiang Mai,
you have to let me
handle the major cases.
You're this soft.
Can you really handle it?
Third,
after we get divorced,
you have to tell your father
to transfer me
to Mueang Phayao Police Station.
Is that a deal?
Otherwise, you can take your ring back.
I'm not the one in trouble anyway.
Whoa, whoa, hey!
Calm down.
As soon as the curse is gone,
we divorce immediately.
Deal.
(Marriage Certificate)
And just like that,
you're officially a married couple.
So, we're all set now, right?
Not yet, dear.
It's just the paperwork done.
We still need the wedding ceremony
and the soul-binding ritual.
Is that really necessary, Mom?
Heaven and earth already know,
and so does the government.
No can do, son.
You have to make it look like
you're really a couple.
Alright, if you're ready,
allow me to introduce the grooms.
At this very moment,
the sun is positioned directly
over this sacred ground.
It's a sign of the auspicious hour
for both grooms to exchange rings,
recite your vows to each other,
and promise to keep those vows
from this moment on.
I promise...
to be a loving...
and faithful husband to Mungkorn.
I promise to be a good husband
to share in both joy and sorrow
and never leave your side.
Mungkorn,
I'm so grateful
that you agreed to marry Thear.
Even if you don't have feelings
for each other yet,
I hope you'll grow to love one another
and stay destined for each other
like this forever.
Now that you're married,
you'd better cut out the womanizing.
Jeez, Dad. What kind of person
do you take me for?
A decent person.
Come on, honey.
He is.
Please take good care of Mungkorn,
Inspector Thear.
Always talk things through
when you have problems.
In a marriage, if one is fire,
the other must be water.
Okay, Mom.
I'm ready to be the fire...
that burns Mungkorn up.
And I'll be the water...
to drown Inspector Thear in.
Remember this.
After the ceremony is over,
you two must share a bed
and become one
in the most intimate way.
Otherwise,
this soul-binding will not be complete,
and fate will continue to haunt you.
You two must love each other
as much as you possibly can
for the heavens and earth
are watching you.
Next,
give each other a tender kiss
to seal your love.
Kiss... now.
Kiss! Kiss!
- Just kiss him, son.
- Kiss! Kiss!
You're good at it, aren't you?
Kiss! Kiss!
Kiss him already.
For the next part of the ceremony,
we ask the parents of the grooms
to escort the newlyweds
to their wedding chamber.
We have to go to
the wedding chamber together?
Well, of course, Mr. Mungkorn!
Tonight, you have to sleep
in Mr. Thear's room.
Most importantly,
you must stay together all night.
You are strictly forbidden
from leaving the room.
Is the closet space enough for you?
If it's not, just let me know.
It's not like I'm moving in permanently.
This is more than enough.
And why are you wearing those pajamas?
They look so worn out.
Do you want to wear some of mine?
No, thanks.
I'm used to these.
But don't worry.
They're definitely clean.
If you're done, please go get dressed
so I can set up the bed.
Go ahead, then.
Why?
Are you blushing?
Don't be ridiculous.
I've got it, too. Why would I?
Exactly, why would you?
I'll just make myself comfortable, then.
Might as well strip down completely.
Hey, I'm your husband now.
Seeing a bit of each other is fine.
I don't mind.
Well, I do.
Don't forget, Inspector,
that you're just a counterfeit husband.
It's fake, you know.
Please, it's not like
I'm actually attracted to you.
Once this marriage
to fix my luck is over,
I'll have to mend the hearts
of all the girls lining up for me.
Man, the line is never-ending.
It's longer
than the stairway to Doi Suthep.
Whatever you say.
And if it really is that long,
then I wish them a blessed pilgrimage.
Why are you sleeping over there?
Come here and sleep on the bed.
I prefer sleeping by myself.
I don't like sharing a bed with anyone.
What do you mean "anyone"?
It's just me.
We've known each other for ages.
The more I know you,
the less I want to share a bed with you.
Inspector, that hurts!
Stop calling me "Inspector."
Why don't you try calling me...
husband?
Alright, Husband.
Can we go to sleep now?
If you want to come up here,
I don't mind.
You could even sneak a hug.
I'm always ready to do that.
I'm not buying that.
♪Trying...♪
Good night, "Husband."
Am I doing the right thing here?
♪I'm just a name on your contract,
you're just passing through,♪
♪So stay on your side,
and I'll stay on mine, too♪
♪Trying so hard not to cross the line,♪
♪But the more I run,
the more you're on my mind♪
♪If you're gonna love me,
don't break the deal we made♪
♪Don't break my heart,
remember what you said?♪
♪It's time you became mine♪
What are you doing in here?
Afraid I'll see your willy?
I've never been with anyone like this.
You'd better get used to it.
I mean my body.
Inspector, are you okay?
Of course I am.
We'll only act like lovey-dovey husbands
at home.
Once we're outside,
we're just boss and subordinate.
And don't tell anyone about this.
I'm here to remind you
about the promise.
You said once we got married,
you'd let me handle the major cases.
What if I break that promise?
Will you tell everyone...
Inspector Thear and I are...
♪Trying so hard not to cross the line,♪
♪But the more I run,
the more you're on my mind♪
♪If you're gonna love me,
don't break the deal we made♪
♪Don't break my heart,
remember what you said?♪
♪Let's call off the deal
and let our hearts decide♪
♪From contracting parties to lovers,
does that sound alright?♪
♪It's time you became mine♪